International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Records on Microfilm 5432 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Brotherhood of Pulp Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Records on Microfilm
1906-1957
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers
5432 mf
31.78 cubic feet
286 microfilm reels
Records (documents), microfilm.
These papers of the IBPSPMW cover most of the years from 1906, the year of the organization of the International Brotherhood, to 1957. Files for a few years are missing.
16213564
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 26, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 12, 2019
Scope and Contents
Microfilm copies of the files of the International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers.
This collection consists primarily of the President-Secretary's files.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6030: Archival Collective Bargaining Agreements File 6046: Archives Union File (AUF) 5097: New York State Board of Mediation and Arbitration Transcripts and Exhibits 5288: International Brotherhood Pulp, Sulphite, Paper Mill Workers, Local 670 (Utica, NY) Minute Book
Paper industry workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Collective bargaining -- Paper industry; International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers
16213564
- 1906: Reel no.1 (Reel 1)
  - Officers, 1906; 1 (Reel 1)
  - Local Unions-Bellows Falls, 1906; 2 (Reel 1)
  - Local Unions-Cadyville, 1906; 3 (Reel 1)
  - Local Unions-Mechanicsville, 1906; 4 (Reel 1)
  - Local Unions-Morrisonville, 1906; 5 (Reel 1)
- 1906: Reel no.2 (Reel 2)
  - Local Unions - Niagara Falls, 1906; 1 (Reel 2)
  - International Unions, 1906; 2 (Reel 2)
  - Federations, 1906; 3 (Reel 2)
  - Companies-Bondin Paper Co., 1906; 4 (Reel 2)
  - Companies-Union Bag & Paper Co., 1906; 5 (Reel 2)
- 1907: Reel no.1 (Reel 3)
  - Officers, 1907; 1 (Reel 3)
  - Local Unions-Ballston Spa, 1907; 2 (Reel 3)
  - Local Unions-Cascade, 1907; 3 (Reel 3)
  - Local Unions-Franklin, 1907; 4 (Reel 3)
  - Local Unions-Livemore Fells, 1907; 5 (Reel 3)
- 1907: Reel no.2 (Reel 4)
  - Local Unions-Luzerne, 1907; 1 (Reel 4)
  - Local Unions-Millinocket, 1907; 2 (Reel 4)
  - Local Unions-Orono, 1907; 3 (Reel 4)
  - Local Unions-Sandy Hill, 1907; 4 (Reel 4)
  - Local Unions-Ticonderoga, 1907; 5 (Reel 4)
- 1907: Reel no.3 (Reel 5)
  - Local Unions-Wilder, 1907; 1 (Reel 5)
  - International Unions, 1907; 2 (Reel 5)
  - Federations, 1907; 3 (Reel 5)
  - Companies-Gt. Northern Paper Co., 1907; 4 (Reel 5)
  - Companies-St. Croix Paper Co., 1907; 5 (Reel 5)
- 1908: Reel no.1 (Reel 6)
  - Officers, 1908; 1 (Reel 6)
  - Local Unions-Ballston Spa, 1908; 2 (Reel 6)
  - International Union-Stationary Fireman, 1908; 3 (Reel 6)
  - Federations-A. F. of L., 1908; 4 (Reel 6)
  - Companies-Gt. Northern Paper Co., 1908; 5 (Reel 6)
  - Companies - General, 1908; 6 (Reel 6)
- 1909: Reel no.1 (Reel 7)
  - Files for the Year 1909 are missing, 1 (Reel 7)
- 1910: Reel no.1 (Reel 8)
  - Files for the Year 1910 are missing, 1 (Reel 8)
- 1911: Reel no.1 (Reel 9)
  - Officers, 1911; 1 (Reel 9)
  - Local Unions-Ballston Spa, 1911; 2 (Reel 9)
  - International Unions, 1911; 3 (Reel 9)
  - Federations, 1911; 4 (Reel 9)
  - Companies-E-Z Spener Bug Co., 1911; 5 (Reel 9)
  - Companies - Associations, 1911; 6 (Reel 9)
- 1912: Reel no.1 (Reel 10)
  - Officers, 1912; 1 (Reel 10)
  - Local Unions - Agusta, 1912; 2 (Reel 10)
  - Local Unions-Northampton, 1912; 3 (Reel 10)
  - Local Unions-Watertown, 1912; 4 (Reel 10)
- 1912: Reel no.2 (Reel 11)
  - Local Unions-Wilder, 1912; 1 (Reel 11)
  - International Unions Paper Makers, 1912; 2 (Reel 11)
  - Federations-A. F. of L., 1912; 3 (Reel 11)
  - Companies-Gt. Northern Paper Co., 1912; 4 (Reel 11)
  - Companies-St. Regis Paper Co., 1912; 5 (Reel 11)
- 1913: Reel no.1 (Reel 12)
  - Officers, 1913; 1 (Reel 12)
  - Local Unions-Augusta, 1913; 2 (Reel 12)
  - Local Unions-Livermore Falls, 1913; 3 (Reel 12)
  - Local Unions-Pyrites, 1913; 4 (Reel 12)
- 1913: Reel no.2 (Reel 13)
  - Local Unions-Pierce Field, 1913; 1 (Reel 13)
  - International Unions-Machinists, 1913; 2 (Reel 13)
  - Federations-A. F. of L., 1913; 3 (Reel 13)
  - Companies-Aldrich Paper Co., 1913; 4 (Reel 13)
  - Companies-Union Bag & Paper Co., 1913; 5 (Reel 13)
- 1914: Reel no.1 (Reel 14)
  - Officers, 1914; 1 (Reel 14)
  - Local Unions-Augusta, 1914; 2 (Reel 14)
  - Local Unions-Livermore Falls, 1914; 3 (Reel 14)
  - Local Unions-Riley, 1914; 4 (Reel 14)
  - Local Unions-Turners Falls, 1914; 5 (Reel 14)
- 1914: Reel no.2 (Reel 15)
  - Local Unions-Watertown, 1914; 1 (Reel 15)
  - International Unions-Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers, 1914; 2 (Reel 15)
  - Federations-A. F. of L., 1914; 3 (Reel 15)
  - Companies - Anglo-Newfoundland Co., 1914; 4 (Reel 15)
  - Companies-Miscrlla, 1914; 5 (Reel 15)
- 1915: Reel no.1 (Reel 16)
  - Officers, 1915; 1 (Reel 16)
  - Local Unions-Augusta, 1915; 2 (Reel 16)
  - Local Union-East Millinocket, 1915; 3 (Reel 16)
  - Local Unions-Groveton, 1915; 4 (Reel 16)
  - Local Unions-Piercefield, 1915; 5 (Reel 16)
- 1915: Reel no.2 (Reel 17)
  - Local Union-Pyrites, 1915; 1 (Reel 17)
  - International Unions- Machinists, 1915; 2 (Reel 17)
  - Federation-A. F. of L., 1915; 3 (Reel 17)
  - Companies - Grand Lakes Paper Co., 1915; 4 (Reel 17)
  - Companies - General, 1915; 5 (Reel 17)
- 1916: Reel no.1 (Reel 18)
  - Officers, 1916; 1 (Reel 18)
  - Local Unions-Appleton, 1916; 2 (Reel 18)
  - Local Unions-Fort Edwards, 1916; 3 (Reel 18)
  - Local Unions - Hudson Falls, 1916; 4 (Reel 18)
  - Local Unions-Milton, 1916; 5 (Reel 18)
- 1916: Reel no.2 (Reel 19)
  - Local Unions-Morrisonville, 1916; 1 (Reel 19)
  - Local Unions-Rumford, 1916; 2 (Reel 19)
  - Local Unions - Topsham, 1916; 3 (Reel 19)
  - International Unions-Paper Makers, 1916; 4 (Reel 19)
  - Federations-A. F. of L., 1916; 5 (Reel 19)
  - Companies-Booth Paper Co., 1916; 6 (Reel 19)
  - Companies-Associations, 1916; 7 (Reel 19)
- 1917: Reel no.1 (Reel 20)
  - Officers, 1917; 1 (Reel 20)
  - Officers-Joseph Tylkoff, 1917; 2 (Reel 20)
  - Local Unions-Appleton, 1917; 3 (Reel 20)
  - Local Unions-Groveton, 1917; 4 (Reel 20)
  - Local Unions-Livermore Falls, 1917; 5 (Reel 20)
- 1917: Reel no.2 (Reel 21)
  - Local Unions-Madison, 1917; 1 (Reel 21)
  - Local Unions-Piercefield, 1917; 2 (Reel 21)
  - Local Unions-Thorold, 1917; 3 (Reel 21)
  - International Unions-Carpenters, 1917; 4 (Reel 21)
  - Federations-Allied Printing Trade Council, 1917; 5 (Reel 21)
  - Other Organizations, 1917; 6 (Reel 21)
  - Companies-Cherry River Paper Co., 1917; 7 (Reel 21)
  - Companies-Associations, 1917; 8 (Reel 21)
- 1918: Reel no.1 (Reel 22)
  - Officers, 1918; 1 (Reel 22)
  - Officers-Herbert W. Sullivan, 1918; 2 (Reel 22)
  - Local Unions-Appleton, 1918; 3 (Reel 22)
  - Local Unions-Grand Falls, 1918; 4 (Reel 22)
  - Local Unions-Little Chute, 1918; 5 (Reel 22)
- 1918: Reel no.2 (Reel 23)
  - Local Unions-Livermore Falls, 1918; 1 (Reel 23)
  - Local Unions-Sault St. Marie, 1918; 2 (Reel 23)
  - International Unions-United Brotherhood of Carpenters, 1918; 3 (Reel 23)
  - Federation-A. F. of L., 1918; 4 (Reel 23)
  - Companies-Abitibi Hover end Paper Co., 1918; 5 (Reel 23)
  - Companies-Associations, 1918; 6 (Reel 23)
- 1919: Reel no.1 (Reel 24)
  - Officers, 1919; 1 (Reel 24)
  - Officers-Launer, Edward, 1919; 2 (Reel 24)
  - Organizers-Cox, J. H., 1919; 3 (Reel 24)
  - Local Unions-Appleton, 1919; 4 (Reel 24)
  - Local Unions-Appleton, 1919; 5 (Reel 24)
- 1919: Reel no.2 (Reel 25)
  - Local Unions-Augusta, 1919; 1 (Reel 25)
  - Local Unions-East Angus, 1919; 2 (Reel 25)
  - Local Unions - Madison, 1919; 3 (Reel 25)
  - Local Unions-Pejepscot, 1919; 4 (Reel 25)
  - Local Unions-Rhinelander, 1919; 5 (Reel 25)
- 1919: Reel no.3 (Reel 26)
  - Local Unions-Richwood, 1919; 1 (Reel 26)
  - Local Unions-Ticonderoga, 1919; 2 (Reel 26)
  - International Unions-United Brotherhood of Carpenters, 1919; 3 (Reel 26)
  - Federations - Allied Printing Trades Council of Greater New York, 1919; 4 (Reel 26)
  - Companies - Abitibi Power and Paper Co., 1919; 5 (Reel 26)
  - Companies - Associations, 1919; 6 (Reel 26)
- 1920: Reel no.1 (Reel 27)
  - Officers, 1920; 1 (Reel 27)
  - Officers - McMahon, Thomas, 1920; 2 (Reel 27)
  - Officers-Stephen, Jacob, 1920; 3 (Reel 27)
  - Officers - Stephen, Jacob, 1920; 4 (Reel 27)
- 1920: Reel no.2 (Reel 28)
  - Officers-Talbot, Troxtom, 1920; 1 (Reel 28)
  - Local Unions-Appleton, 1920; 2 (Reel 28)
  - Local Unions-Exploits River, 1920; 3 (Reel 28)
  - Local Unions-Kalamazoo, 1920; 4 (Reel 28)
  - Local Unions-Little Falls, 1920; 5 (Reel 28)
- 1920: Reel no.3 (Reel 29)
  - Local Unions-Livermore Falls, 1920; 1 (Reel 29)
  - Local Unions-Richwood, 1920; 2 (Reel 29)
  - International Unions & Federations-International Assoc. of Machinists, 1920; 3 (Reel 29)
  - Companies-Abitibi Paper Co., 1920; 4 (Reel 29)
  - Companies - Associations, 1920; 5 (Reel 29)
- 1921: Reel no.1 (Reel 30)
  - Officers, 1921; 1 (Reel 30)
  - Officers-LaBelle, Maurice, 1921; 2 (Reel 30)
  - Officers-Sullivan, H. W., 1921; 3 (Reel 30)
  - Officers-Stephan, Jacob, 1921; 4 (Reel 30)
  - Officers-Circular Letters to all local unions, 1921; 5 (Reel 30)
- 1921: Reel no.2 (Reel 31)
  - Officers-Circular Letters to all local unions, 1921; 1 (Reel 31)
  - Local Unions-Appleton, 1921; 2 (Reel 31)
  - Local Unions-Espanola, 1921; 3 (Reel 31)
  - Local Unions-Glens Falls, 1921; 4 (Reel 31)
  - Local Unions-Hull, 1921; 5 (Reel 31)
- 1921: Reel no.3 (Reel 32)
  - Local Unions-International, 1921; 1 (Reel 32)
  - Local Unions - Marathon, 1921; 2 (Reel 32)
  - Local Unions-Mekoosa, 1921; 3 (Reel 32)
  - Local Unions-Pejepscot, 1921; 4 (Reel 32)
  - Local Unions-Piercefield, 1921; 5 (Reel 32)
- 1921: Reel no.4 (Reel 33)
  - Local Unions-Port Arthur, 1921; 1 (Reel 33)
  - Local Unions-River Du Loup, 1921; 2 (Reel 33)
  - Local Unions-Sturgeon Falls, 1921; 3 (Reel 33)
  - Local Unions-Windsor Hills, 1921; 4 (Reel 33)
  - International Unions -Amalgamated Clothing Workers, 1921; 5 (Reel 33)
  - International Unions-International Brotherhood of Paper Makers, 1921; 6 (Reel 33)
- 1921: Reel no.5 (Reel 34)
  - International Unions-International Brotherhood of Paper Makers J. T. Carey, 1921; 1 (Reel 34)
  - Federations-Allied Printing Trades Council of New York State, 1921; 2 (Reel 34)
  - Companies-Abitibi Power and Paper Co., 1921; 3 (Reel 34)
  - Companies - Associations, 1921; 4 (Reel 34)
- 1922: Reel no.1 (Reel 35)
  - Officers, 1922; 1 (Reel 35)
  - Officers-Laumer, S. F., 1922; 2 (Reel 35)
  - Officers - Stephen, Jacob, 1922; 3 (Reel 35)
  - Local Unions - Alexandria Bay, 1922; 4 (Reel 35)
  - Local Unions - Continental Paper Bag Makers, 1922; 5 (Reel 35)
- 1922: Reel no.2 (Reel 36)
  - Local Unions - Continental Paper Bag Makers (cont.), 1922; 1 (Reel 36)
  - Local Unions-Grand Falls, 1922; 2 (Reel 36)
  - Local Unions-Lincoln, 1922; 3 (Reel 36)
  - Local Unions-Milton, 1922; 4 (Reel 36)
- 1922: Reel no.3 (Reel 37)
  - Local Unions-Miramichi, 1922; 1 (Reel 37)
  - Local Unions-Pejpscot, 1922; 2 (Reel 37)
  - Local Unions-St. Regis, 1922; 3 (Reel 37)
  - Local Unions-Van Buren, 1922; 4 (Reel 37)
  - Local Unions-Watertown, 1922; 5 (Reel 37)
- 1922: Reel no.4 (Reel 38)
  - Local Unions-West Enfield, 1922; 1 (Reel 38)
  - International Unions-International Brotherhood of Electric Workers, 1922; 2 (Reel 38)
  - Federations-Allied Printing Trades Council of New York State, 1922; 3 (Reel 38)
  - Companies -Abitibi Power and Paper Co., 1922; 4 (Reel 38)
  - Companies-Associations, 1922; 5 (Reel 38)
- 1923: Reel no.1 (Reel 39)
  - Officers, 1923; 1 (Reel 39)
  - Officers-Laumer, S. E., 1923; 2 (Reel 39)
  - Officers-Taylor, J. W., 1923; 3 (Reel 39)
  - Local Unions-Appleton, 1923; 4 (Reel 39)
  - Local Unions-Edmunston, 1923; 5 (Reel 39)
- 1923: Reel no.2 (Reel 40)
  - Local Unions-Escamaba, 1923; 1 (Reel 40)
  - International Unions-Kaujauma, 1923; 2 (Reel 40)
  - International Unions-Norfolk, 1923; 3 (Reel 40)
  - International Unions-Paper Box Makers Union of Greater New York, 1923; 4 (Reel 40)
  - International Unions-Port Edward Howland 87 located at end of roll, 1923; 5 (Reel 40)
- 1923: Reel no.3 (Reel 41)
  - International Unions-Pyrites, 1923; 1 (Reel 41)
  - Federations- Affiliated Building Trades, 1923; 2 (Reel 41)
  - Companies-Abitibi Power and Paper Co., 1923; 3 (Reel 41)
  - Companies-International Paper Co., 1923; 4 (Reel 41)
  - Companies- Associations, 1923; 5 (Reel 41)
- 1924: Reel no.1 (Reel 42)
  - Officers, 1924; 1 (Reel 42)
  - Officers-Sullivan, H. W., 1924; 2 (Reel 42)
  - Officers-Vamier, John, 1924; 3 (Reel 42)
  - Local Unions-Augusta, 1924; 4 (Reel 42)
  - Local Unions-Hudson River, 1924; 5 (Reel 42)
- 1924: Reel no.2 (Reel 43)
  - Local Unions-International Falls, 1924; 1 (Reel 43)
  - Local Unions-Orono, 1924; 2 (Reel 43)
  - International Unions-Amal. Assoc. of Iron Workers, 1924; 3 (Reel 43)
  - Federations-Allied Printing Trades Council of New York State, 1924; 4 (Reel 43)
  - Federations-General Files, 1924; 5 (Reel 43)
- 1924: Reel no.3 (Reel 44)
  - Federations-General Files, 1924; 1 (Reel 44)
  - Companies-Abitibi Power and Paper Co., 1924; 2 (Reel 44)
  - Companies - Associations, 1924; 3 (Reel 44)
- 1925: Reel no.1 (Reel 45)
  - Officers, 1925; 1 (Reel 45)
  - Officer-Launer, S. E., 1925; 2 (Reel 45)
  - Officers-Executive Board, 1925; 3 (Reel 45)
  - Officers-Vamier, John, 1925; 4 (Reel 45)
  - Local Unions - Appleton, 1925; 5 (Reel 45)
  - Local Unions- Escamba, 1925; 6 (Reel 45)
- 1925: Reel no.2 (Reel 46)
  - Local Unions-Espanola, 1925; 1 (Reel 46)
  - Local Unions-Marinette, 1925; 2 (Reel 46)
  - Local Unions-Port Arthur, 1925; 3 (Reel 46)
  - International Unions-United Brotherhood of Carpenters of America, 1925; 4 (Reel 46)
  - Federations-A. F. of L, 1925; 5 (Reel 46)
- 1925: Reel no.3 (Reel 47)
  - Federations-A. F. of L. Marks, A, 1925; 1 (Reel 47)
  - Companies-Abitibi Power and Paper Co., 1925; 2 (Reel 47)
  - Companies - Associations, 1925; 3 (Reel 47)
- 1926: Reel no.1 (Reel 48)
  - Officers, 1926; 1 (Reel 48)
  - Officers- Sullivan, H. W., 1926; 2 (Reel 48)
  - Officers-Stephan, Jacob, 1926; 3 (Reel 48)
  - Local Unions-Augusta, 1926; 4 (Reel 48)
  - Local Unions-Fort Frances, 1926; 5 (Reel 48)
- 1926: Reel no.2 (Reel 49)
  - Local Unions-Grand Falls, 1926; 1 (Reel 49)
  - Local Unions-Norfolk, 1926; 2 (Reel 49)
  - Local Unions-Three Rivers, 1926; 3 (Reel 49)
  - International Unions-International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, 1926; 4 (Reel 49)
  - Federations-Allied Printing Trade Council of New York State, 1926; 5 (Reel 49)
  - Federations-General Files, 1926; 6 (Reel 49)
- 1926: Reel no.3 (Reel 50)
  - Companies-.Abitibi Power and Paper Co., 1926; 1 (Reel 50)
  - Companies-Associations, 1926; 2 (Reel 50)
- 1927: Reel no.1 (Reel 51)
  - Officers, 1927; 1 (Reel 51)
  - Officers-Labelle, Maurice, 1927; 2 (Reel 51)
  - Officers-Sullivan, H.W., 1927; 3 (Reel 51)
  - Local Unions-Appleton, 1927; 4 (Reel 51)
  - Local Unions - International Falls, 1927; 5 (Reel 51)
- 1927: Reel no.2 (Reel 52)
  - Local Unions - Iroquois Falls, 1927; 1 (Reel 52)
  - International Unions-United Brotherhood of Carpenters, 1927; 2 (Reel 52)
  - Federations - Allied Printing Trades Council of New York State, 1927; 3 (Reel 52)
  - Companies - Abitibi Power and Paper Co., 1927; 4 (Reel 52)
  - Companies - Associations, 1927; 5 (Reel 52)
- 1928: Reel no.1 (Reel 53)
  - Officers, 1928; 1 (Reel 53)
  - Officers - LaBelle, Maurice, 1928; 2 (Reel 53)
  - Officers-Parker, M.H., 1928; 3 (Reel 53)
  - Officers- Stephan, Jacob, 1928; 4 (Reel 53)
- 1928: Reel no.2 (Reel 54)
  - Officers-Conference Reports, 1928; 1 (Reel 54)
  - Local Unions - Augusta, 1928; 2 (Reel 54)
  - Local Unions-Lishon Falle, 1928; 3 (Reel 54)
  - Local Unions-Thorold, 1928; 4 (Reel 54)
  - Local Unions-Pulp Sulphite Councils, 1928; 5 (Reel 54)
- 1928: Reel no.3 (Reel 55)
  - International Unions-American Federations of Musicians, 1928; 1 (Reel 55)
  - Federations-Allied Printing Trade Council of New York State, 1928; 2 (Reel 55)
  - Companies-Abititi Power and Light Co., 1928; 3 (Reel 55)
  - Companies - Associations, 1928; 4 (Reel 55)
- 1929: Reel no.1 (Reel 56)
  - President Secretary Files, 1929; 1 (Reel 56)
  - Officers-Kruegar, A. C., 1929; 2 (Reel 56)
  - Officers-Launer, S. C., 1929; 3 (Reel 56)
  - Executive Board, 1929; 4 (Reel 56)
  - Local Unions-Corner Brook, 1929; 5 (Reel 56)
- 1929: Reel no.2 (Reel 57)
  - Local Unions-Dominion, 1929; 1 (Reel 57)
  - Local Unions-Kapuskasing, 1929; 2 (Reel 57)
  - Local Unions-Saulte Ste. Marie, 1929; 3 (Reel 57)
  - Local Unions-Twin City, 1929; 4 (Reel 57)
- 1929: Reel no.3 (Reel 58)
  - Local Unions-Weddington, 1929; 1 (Reel 58)
  - Government, 1929; 2 (Reel 58)
  - Company Associations, 1929; 3 (Reel 58)
- 1930: Reel no.1 (Reel 59)
  - President Secretary Files, 1930; 1 (Reel 59)
  - Officers-LaPelle, Maurice, 1930; 2 (Reel 59)
  - Organizers-Sample, C.H., 1930; 3 (Reel 59)
  - Special Organizers-Gibson, A., 1930; 4 (Reel 59)
  - Local Unions-Grand Mere, 1930; 5 (Reel 59)
- 1930: Reel no.2 (Reel 60)
  - Local Unions-Great Lakes, 1930; 1 (Reel 60)
  - Local Unions-Lisbon Falls, 1930; 2 (Reel 60)
  - Local Unions-St. Regis, 1930; 3 (Reel 60)
  - Int. Unions, 1930; 4 (Reel 60)
  - Company Associations, 1930; 5 (Reel 60)
- 1931: Reel no.1 (Reel 61)
  - President Secretary Files, 1931; 1 (Reel 61)
  - Officers-Taylor, J.W., 1931; 2 (Reel 61)
  - Special Organizers - Ashton, S., 1931; 3 (Reel 61)
  - Local Unions-Lisbon Falls, 1931; 4 (Reel 61)
  - Local Unions-Merriton, 1931; 5 (Reel 61)
- 1931: Reel no.2 (Reel 62)
  - Local Unions-Millinocket, 1931; 1 (Reel 62)
  - Local Unions-Tsin City, 1931; 2 (Reel 62)
  - Local Unions-Int. Brotherhood of Paper Makers, 1931; 3 (Reel 62)
  - General Files-Newspapers, 1931; 4 (Reel 62)
  - Company Associations, 1931; 5 (Reel 62)
- 1932: Reel no.1 (Reel 63)
  - President Secretary Filer, 1932; 1 (Reel 63)
  - Officer - Sullivan, F. W., 1932; 2 (Reel 63)
  - Special Organizers - Addy j., 1932; 3 (Reel 63)
  - Local Unions-Kanora, 1932; 4 (Reel 63)
  - Local Unions-Millinocket, 1932; 5 (Reel 63)
- 1932: Reel no.2 (Reel 64)
  - Local Unions-Munisinc, 1932; 1 (Reel 64)
  - Prospective Locals, 1932; 2 (Reel 64)
  - Unions-Typographical Union, 1932; 3 (Reel 64)
  - General Files-Olzendam, R., 1932; 4 (Reel 64)
  - Company Associations, 1932; 5 (Reel 64)
- 1933: Reel no.1 (Reel 65)
  - President Secretary Files, 1933; 1 (Reel 65)
  - Officers-Henke, R.C., 1933; 2 (Reel 65)
  - Executive Board, 1933; 3 (Reel 65)
  - Local Unions-Atholville, 1933; 4 (Reel 65)
  - Local Unions-Covington, 1933; 5 (Reel 65)
- 1933: Reel no.2 (Reel 66)
  - Local Unions-Dalhousie, 1933; 1 (Reel 66)
  - Local Unions-Hodge, 1933; 2 (Reel 66)
  - Local Unions-Luke, 1933; 3 (Reel 66)
  - Local Unions-Port Townsend, 1933; 4 (Reel 66)
  - Local Unions-Rumford, 1933; 5 (Reel 66)
- 1933: Reel no.3 (Reel 67)
  - Local Unions-St. Helens, 1933; 1 (Reel 67)
  - Local Unions-Wood City, 1933; 2 (Reel 67)
  - Unions-Operating Engineers, 1933; 3 (Reel 67)
  - Government-United states, 1933; 4 (Reel 67)
  - Company Associations, 1933; 5 (Reel 67)
- 1934: Reel no.1 (Reel 68)
  - President Secretary Files, 1934; 1 (Reel 68)
  - Officers-Doddy, Bat, 1934; 2 (Reel 68)
  - Officers-Stephens, S. A., 1934; 3 (Reel 68)
  - Officers - Mangam, E.A., 1934; 4 (Reel 68)
  - Officers-Richards, R., 1934; 5 (Reel 68)
- 1934: Reel no.2 (Reel 69)
  - Organizers-Stephan, J., 1934; 1 (Reel 69)
  - Circular Letters, 1934; 2 (Reel 69)
  - Local Unions-Augusta, 1934; 3 (Reel 69)
  - Local Unions-Cloquet, 1934; 4 (Reel 69)
  - Local Unions-Local Brook, 1934; 5 (Reel 69)
- 1934: Reel no.3 (Reel 70)
  - Local Unions - Covington, 1934; 1 (Reel 70)
  - Local Unions-Fall River, 1934; 2 (Reel 70)
  - Local Unions-Howland, 1934; 3 (Reel 70)
  - Local Unions-Luke, 1934; 4 (Reel 70)
  - Local Unions - Nira, 1934; 5 (Reel 70)
- 1934: Reel no.4 (Reel 71)
  - Local Unions-Norfolk, 1934; 1 (Reel 71)
  - LocaI Unions-Paper Plate & Bag Makers, 1934; 2 (Reel 71)
  - Local UnionsPort Townsend, 1934; 3 (Reel 71)
  - Local Unions-Rumford, Mexico, 1934; 4 (Reel 71)
  - Local Unions-Sand Springs, 1934; 5 (Reel 71)
- 1934: Reel no.5 (Reel 72)
  - Local Unions- Sandusky, 1934; 1 (Reel 72)
  - Local Unions-Vancouver, 1934; 2 (Reel 72)
  - Unions-Addy, J., 1934; 3 (Reel 72)
  - Unions-Sheep Shearers Union of N. America, 1934; 4 (Reel 72)
  - Government-United States, 1934; 5 (Reel 72)
- 1934: Reel no.6 (Reel 73)
  - Government-United States, 1934; 1 (Reel 73)
  - Companies - St. Croix Paper Co., 1934; 2 (Reel 73)
  - Company Associations, 1934; 3 (Reel 73)
- 1935: Reel no.1 (Reel 74)
  - President Secretary files, 1935; 1 (Reel 74)
  - Officers, Doody, Bat, 1935; 2 (Reel 74)
  - Officers, Stephens, S. A., 1935; 3 (Reel 74)
  - Organizers-Barnes, F., 1935; 4 (Reel 74)
  - Organizers-Mangan, E. A., 1935; 5 (Reel 74)
- 1935: Reel no.2 (Reel 75)
  - Organizers-Stephan, J, 1935; 1 (Reel 75)
  - Locals-Akron, 1935; 2 (Reel 75)
  - Locals-Cincinnati, 1935; 3 (Reel 75)
  - Locals-Dominion, 1935; 4 (Reel 75)
  - Locals-Hudson River, 1935; 5 (Reel 75)
- 1935: Reel no.3 (Reel 76)
  - Local Unions-International Falls, 1935; 1 (Reel 76)
  - Local Unions-Lebanon, 1935; 2 (Reel 76)
  - Local Unions-Milwaukee, 1935; 3 (Reel 76)
  - Local Unions-Port Angeles, 1935; 4 (Reel 76)
  - Local Unions-St. Lawrence, 1935; 5 (Reel 76)
- 1935: Reel no.4 (Reel 77)
  - Locals-St. Regis, 1935; 1 (Reel 77)
  - Locals-Utica, 1935; 2 (Reel 77)
  - Unions-Morrison, F., 1935; 3 (Reel 77)
  - Other Organizations-Socialist Party, 1935; 4 (Reel 77)
- 1935: Reel no.5 (Reel 78)
  - Other Organizations-Socialist Party, 1935; 1 (Reel 78)
  - Companies, 1935; 2 (Reel 78)
  - Company Associations, 1935; 3 (Reel 78)
- 1936: Reel no.1 (Reel 79)
  - President Secretary Files, 1936; 1 (Reel 79)
  - Officers-LaBelle. Maurice, 1936; 2 (Reel 79)
  - Officers-Sherman, John, 1936; 3 (Reel 79)
  - Officers-Taylor, J. H., 1936; 4 (Reel 79)
  - Organizers-Leon, R., 1936; 5 (Reel 79)
- 1936: Reel no.2 (Reel 80)
  - Organizers-Mangam, E., 1936; 1 (Reel 80)
  - Organizers-Stephan, J, 1936; 2 (Reel 80)
  - Circular Letters, 1936; 3 (Reel 80)
  - Local Unions-Dominion, 1936; 4 (Reel 80)
  - Local Unions-International Falls, 1936; 5 (Reel 80)
- 1936: Reel no.3 (Reel 81)
  - Locals-Iroquois Falls, 1936; 1 (Reel 81)
  - Locals-Milwaukee, 1936; 2 (Reel 81)
  - Locals - Pejepscot, 1936; 3 (Reel 81)
  - Locals-Salem, 1936; 4 (Reel 81)
  - Locals-Toledo, 1936; 5 (Reel 81)
- 1936: Reel no.4 (Reel 82)
  - Local Unions-Tomahawk, 1936; 1 (Reel 82)
  - Other Organizations - Mooney, Tom Defense Comm., 1936; 2 (Reel 82)
  - Company-Beaver Wood Fiber Co., 1936; 3 (Reel 82)
  - Company Associations, 1936; 4 (Reel 82)
- 1937: Reel no.1 (Reel 83)
  - President Secretary Files, 1937; 1 (Reel 83)
  - Officers-Burnell, W.E., 1937; 2 (Reel 83)
  - Officers-Richards, R., 1937; 3 (Reel 83)
  - Officers, Stevens, S. A., 1937; 4 (Reel 83)
  - Officers, Barnes, F. C., 1937; 5 (Reel 83)
- 1937: Reel no.2 (Reel 84)
  - Organizers-Beach, Harry H., 1937; 1 (Reel 84)
  - Organizers-Hoff, A, B., 1937; 2 (Reel 84)
  - Organizers-Louy, L. J., 1937; 3 (Reel 84)
  - Organizers - Sims, B.T., 1937; 4 (Reel 84)
  - Organizers - Stephen, J., 1937; 5 (Reel 84)
- 1937: Reel no.3 (Reel 85)
  - Organizers - Trautman, W., 1937; 1 (Reel 85)
  - Sp. Organizers - Malin, J., 1937; 2 (Reel 85)